<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TheTrashman.com</title>
    <description>You got trashed by TheTrashman.com!</description>
    <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.thetrashman.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 12:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 12:09:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>TOTY 2023 - Teammate Of The Year, Fortnite Squads</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;accepting-the-toty-award-2023-a-milestone-achievement&quot;&gt;Accepting the TOTY Award 2023: A Milestone Achievement&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am incredibly honored and excited to accept the TOTY (Teammate Of The Year) Award for 2023. As TheTrashmanDC (sadly, Epic won’t allow .com in usernames!), I’ve journeyed through countless Fortnite battles, always striving to be the best teammate possible (mostly).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-heartfelt-thank-you&quot;&gt;A Heartfelt Thank You&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, a huge thank you to the academy for this recognition. It means the world to me, especially as a die-hard fan of Tom Hanks, whose incredible performances have always inspired me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;shout-outs-and-appreciation&quot;&gt;Shout Outs and Appreciation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Runner Up&lt;/strong&gt;: A special shout out to Outbraind. Consider this a pity vote, but know it’s also a nod to your impressive skills and teamwork.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last Year’s TOTY&lt;/strong&gt;: Big thanks to Uzbonics for setting the bar. Well, let’s just say you made it easy for me to shine this year!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Voters&lt;/strong&gt;: Immense gratitude to Dirtgrubz and J2Customs. Your votes were pivotal, and I can’t thank you enough for your support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;looking-ahead&quot;&gt;Looking Ahead&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2024 promises to be an exciting year with new TOTY voting mechanics. We’re introducing quarterly voting that will influence the end-of-year decision. This change ensures more engagement and fair recognition of consistent performance throughout the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more updates, and again, thank you all for this incredible honor!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TheTrashmanDC&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images_out/totybattle-800-7dfa0191a.png&quot; srcset=&quot;/assets/images_out/totybattle-200-7dfa0191a.png 200w, /assets/images_out/totybattle-400-7dfa0191a.png 400w, /assets/images_out/totybattle-800-7dfa0191a.png 800w, /assets/images_out/totybattle-1024-7dfa0191a.png 1024w&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;© 2024 TheTrashmanDC. All rights reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/toty-award-for-2023</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/toty-award-for-2023</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
        <category>squad</category>
        
        <category>toty</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to rank up in Fortnite</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortnite, the wildly popular battle royale game developed by Epic Games, has taken the gaming world by storm. With millions of players worldwide, competition in Fortnite is fierce, and every player aspires to achieve higher ranks. If you find yourself struggling to climb the ranks and reach the pinnacle of success, fear not! In this blog post, we will guide you through some essential tips and strategies to help you rank higher in Fortnite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;master-the-basics&quot;&gt;Master the Basics:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before diving into advanced strategies, it is crucial to build a strong foundation. Start by honing your skills in the basics of Fortnite gameplay. Focus on improving your aim, building, and editing techniques. Practice different weapon loadouts and become familiar with their strengths and weaknesses. Developing a solid foundation will set you up for success as you progress further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;drop-smart&quot;&gt;Drop Smart:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choosing the right landing spot is critical for a successful match. While popular locations are tempting due to the abundance of loot, they are also swarming with other players, increasing the likelihood of early confrontations. Instead, opt for lesser-known areas that still offer sufficient loot, allowing you to gather resources and gear up before engaging in combat. This approach gives you a better chance to survive and progress further into the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;resource-management&quot;&gt;Resource Management:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Resources play a vital role in Fortnite. Wood, brick, and metal are essential for building structures to defend yourself or gain a height advantage. Ensure that you gather resources constantly, especially during the early stages of the game. Prioritize harvesting materials from trees, walls, and objects. Efficient resource management will provide you with the necessary materials to outbuild your opponents and secure the high ground advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;strategic-positioning&quot;&gt;Strategic Positioning:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Positioning yourself correctly within the game’s safe zone is crucial for survival and ranking higher. Make a habit of studying the storm circle and plan your movements accordingly. Try to stay ahead of the storm, positioning yourself near its edge to have a better chance of encountering fewer opponents. Additionally, use natural cover to your advantage, such as hills, trees, or buildings, to minimize your exposure and make it harder for enemies to spot and eliminate you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;adaptability&quot;&gt;Adaptability:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortnite is a dynamic game, and every match presents unique challenges. Being adaptable is key to success. Remain flexible in your strategies and playstyle. Adapt to the loot you find, adjusting your loadout and tactics accordingly. Sometimes a stealthy, defensive approach is more effective, while other times, an aggressive playstyle can catch opponents off guard. Learn to read the situation and adjust your strategy accordingly to gain an edge over your adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;communication-and-teamwork&quot;&gt;Communication and Teamwork:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy playing Fortnite in squads or duos, effective communication and teamwork can significantly improve your chances of ranking higher. Utilize in-game voice chat or external communication tools to coordinate with your teammates. Share information about enemy positions, plan attacks, and coordinate building structures. By working together, you can create synergistic strategies and increase your odds of success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;review-and-learn-from-your-matches&quot;&gt;Review and Learn from Your Matches:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To improve your skills and rank higher in Fortnite, take the time to review your gameplay. Analyze your wins and losses to identify areas where you excelled and areas that need improvement. Watch replays to understand your opponents’ strategies and identify any mistakes or missed opportunities. Learning from your mistakes and adapting your gameplay accordingly will accelerate your progress and help you rank higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Climbing the ranks in Fortnite requires a combination of skill, strategy, and adaptability. By mastering the basics, optimizing your landing spots, managing resources, strategically positioning yourself, being adaptable, leveraging communication and teamwork, and reviewing your matches, you’ll be well on your way to ranking higher in Fortnite. Remember, practice and persistence are key, so keep honing your skills and enjoy the exhilarating journey that Fortnite offers. Good luck on your path to victory!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-rank-higher</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-rank-higher</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Improve at Rocket League</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;5-proven-tips-for-improving-your-rocket-league-game&quot;&gt;5 Proven Tips for Improving Your Rocket League Game&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rocket League is a high-speed, high-flying game that requires a combination of skill, strategy, and teamwork. Whether you’re a seasoned player or just starting out, there are many ways to improve your skills and help your team win. Here are five proven tips to help you take your Rocket League game to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Practice basic mechanics: The most important aspect of Rocket League is mastering the basic mechanics, such as dribbling, aerials, and shooting. Start by playing in unranked matches and focusing on improving one specific skill at a time. The more you practice, the more confident you will become in your abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Watch professional players: One of the best ways to improve is to watch how the best players in the world do it. Study their shots, movements, and strategies, and try to incorporate them into your own game. You can find professional Rocket League matches on Twitch or YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Play with friends: Rocket League is a team sport, and playing with friends is one of the best ways to improve your teamwork and communication skills. You can coordinate with your teammates and work together to outmaneuver the other team.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Analyze your replays: After each match, take a few minutes to watch the replay and analyze your performance. Identify areas where you can improve, such as your shot accuracy, positioning, or timing. This will help you to avoid making the same mistakes in future matches.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Stay positive: Finally, it’s important to maintain a positive attitude even when things aren’t going your way. Rocket League can be a very intense and fast-paced game, but staying calm and focused will help you to make better decisions and perform better overall.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, improving at Rocket League takes time, patience, and practice. By following these five tips, you’ll be well on your way to becoming a top-notch player and helping your team win. So get out there, have fun, and good luck!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/rocket-league-tutorial</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/rocket-league-tutorial</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AI Built Fortnite Tutorial</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Fortnite is a popular online game that combines elements of survival, exploration, and building. To win a game of Fortnite, you will need to master a variety of skills, including building, looting, and combat. Here is a basic tutorial on how to play Fortnite and increase your chances of winning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Learn the controls: Before you start playing, familiarize yourself with the game’s controls so that you can move and interact with the environment effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Gather resources: Fortnite is all about survival, and that means gathering resources. You can chop down trees and mine rocks to gather wood, stone, and metal, which you can use to build structures and weapons.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Build structures: Building is an essential part of Fortnite, as it allows you to protect yourself from enemy fire and gain a tactical advantage. You can build walls, ramps, and other structures to create cover and make it harder for enemies to get to you.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Loot: As you explore the map, you will come across various buildings, vehicles, and other structures that you can loot for weapons, ammo, and other useful items. Be sure to check everything you come across to increase your chances of finding useful items.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Combat: Combat is a crucial part of Fortnite, and you’ll need to master the game’s weapons and combat mechanics to have a chance at winning. Try to aim for headshots, and be mindful of your ammo count.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Survive the storm: The storm in Fortnite is a dangerous force that will shrink the playable area of the map over time. Keep an eye on the storm and make sure you’re in a safe location when it closes in.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Play with a team: Playing with a team can be a big advantage in Fortnite, as you can work together to gather resources, build structures, and take out enemies.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Practice, practice, practice: To improve your skills and increase your chances of winning, you’ll need to practice as much as you can. The more you play, the better you will become.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember to always be aware of your surroundings and try different strategies. With time and practice, you will be able to improve your skills and increase your chances of winning.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-tutorial</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-tutorial</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Through the Window</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;That rocket through the window was pretty nice…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Got me&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/rocket-through-the-window</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/rocket-through-the-window</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I ain&apos;t no smurf</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Screw you Kevin, I ain’t no smurf. You’re just that bad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/rocket-league-smurf</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/rocket-league-smurf</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fortnite Glitch, get launched into orbit by a shark</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While playing with the buddies tonight, TheTrashman got booted from the middle of the map all the way out to the edge, ultimately dying in the storm, due to a glitch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently sharks have the ability to launch you into orbit when grabbing on to a vehicle…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-captioned=&quot;&quot; data-instgrm-permalink=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/reel/CkpasrCgYBW/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;14&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:540px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:16px;&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/reel/CkpasrCgYBW/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding: 19% 0;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;&quot;&gt;&lt;svg width=&quot;50px&quot; height=&quot;50px&quot; viewBox=&quot;0 0 60 60&quot; version=&quot;1.1&quot; xmlns=&quot;https://www.w3.org/2000/svg&quot; xmlns:xlink=&quot;https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink&quot;&gt;&lt;g stroke=&quot;none&quot; stroke-width=&quot;1&quot; fill=&quot;none&quot; fill-rule=&quot;evenodd&quot;&gt;&lt;g transform=&quot;translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)&quot; fill=&quot;#000000&quot;&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d=&quot;M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631&quot;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding-top: 8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;&quot;&gt;View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding: 12.5% 0;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;margin-left: 8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;margin-left: auto;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot;display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/reel/CkpasrCgYBW/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading&quot; style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;A post shared by Christopher Hammond (@thechristoc)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//www.instagram.com/embed.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-glitch-shark-launch</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-glitch-shark-launch</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Playstation Failed Fraud Transactions</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Every since TheTrashman got a PS5, he has struggled. Struggled to give Playstation his money. You see, TheTrashman wants to add money to his wallet, so little trashy can purchase Fortnite skins, but Playstation makes it nearly impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TM has reached out to Playstation multiple times to try to get transactions to go through, usually when TM reaches out it starts to work on the web. Yesterday, the Playstation customer support rep suggested trying on the console. TM wasn’t thrilled at this suggestion, but tried it anyways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure enough, both attempted transactions went through fine on the Console.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you’re struggling to try to purchase any games, or add funds, to your Playstation account, try it on the console instead of on the web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doing some request/response inspection, TM was able to determine that for some reason Playstation was declining the web transactions for failing some fraud checks. The question is why? The cards are TMs, have been used before, hell even PayPal was failing the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why would you ever expect the web to work? (FYI Playstation’s website sucks)&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/playstation-fraud-transactions</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/playstation-fraud-transactions</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>playstation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Robbie.com killed TheTrashman.com</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Robbie.com killed TheTrashman.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Fortnite&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/robbie-dot-com</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/robbie-dot-com</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FORTNITE SECRET KLOMBO QUEST</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One quest you won’t find in your quest log in Fortnite is a Secret Klombo question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You basically need to find 3 blow holes in snow mounds. They are all up near the covered bridge, so get searching.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-klombo-quest</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.thetrashman.com/fortnite-klombo-quest</guid>
        
        
        <category>games</category>
        
        <category>fortnite</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
